Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Asta and the rest of the royal knights were busy infiltrating the Eye of the Midnight Sun's hideout.
While Litt, who had just revealed his true identity, was in the royal capital, engaged in a vicious battle with Julius over possession of the magic stones.
But how? What is this strength? He's only human. He shouldn't be able to.
Using his coverless grimoire and time magic abilities, Julius managed to secure the upper hand.
And as the Wizard King, I'll protect the people of Clover, come what may.
However, Litt released himself from his sealing spell to launch a deadly attack on every person in the Clover Kingdom.
The big hunk of light magic. Dammit.
Now, here is your punishment, humans!
Light magic!
Arrows of Judgment!
Time reversal magic!
Chrono Anastasis!
Stay safe!
Julius used all the time and power he'd been saving up to protect the helpless civilians.
But that was exactly what Litt wanted him to do.
You would have seen this attack of mine coming.
But unfortunately, you weren't able to call off that final time magic spell in order to get out of the way.
Because you're...the Wizard King.
What happened to you?
Tell me, Fungence!
How you love!
Here you go.
It's a record of the absolute
You may call me Licked.
You're Licked?
William is lying dormant within this body.
That's right.
You and I both watched it through these eyes, William.
The end of the Wizard King.
What?
If that's the case, then you better say your prayers.
This can't be happening.
There's no way this is real.
Not Julius.
Please, no.
Don't just stand there, Marx.
He's injured.
Go get that quack Owen to come and heal him.
Hurry up!
Right.
Hang tight, Julius.
We've—
Don't bother.
He'll be gone in mere moments now.
You protected your kingdom to the very end.
I must commend you for that, Julius Novachrono.
But.
Master Lick, sir!
The dark magic.
Now dark cloaked.
Elves and humankind will never live in harmony again.
It's over.
Dimension Slash!
He's gone.
Hold on, all right?
Don't die on me!
Yeah, me.
That spell you did was amazing.
You can cut through space itself.
Come on, this is no time for that stuff.
You've turned into a superb magic knight, haven't you?
Julius, like I keep telling you, I'm 28 years old.
I'm not some kid anymore.
It's so inspiring, seeing that your generation was raised right.
And knowing the next one is beginning to budge as well.
My own hopes.
Living on through all of the magic knights to come.
What's wrong, Mr. Third Eye?
Running out of spells?
Yeah, he's finished.
No time to use fast movement or recovery magic.
Try another attack!
I dare you!
We struggled so hard to beat the Third Eye and now look!
Captain Merliona, you're so strong!
If that's really your best, I'll punch you until you're a pile of ashes!
Well, I guess that's it for me.
Now burn!
I'll give you one thing, Miss Royal.
You sure know how to pack Fiery Punch.
Which is why.
Before I burn up, I'm casting a self-destruct spell and taking you down with me!
Once you hit me, we'll disappear with a bang!
That anti-magic brat!
He sniffed out my self-destruct spell and countered it before she landed her attack!
He acted so fast, it's incredible!
Two other people have already tried that!
And I'm fed up with it!
You can't kill yourself on my watch, you three-eyed jerk!
Got it!
Don't throw your life away!
Seriously, what's the matter with you guys?
You're mad at humans for taking something away from you, right?
I'm still fuzzy on the details!
But we're all people!
I want you to tell me your side of the story, and then I'm gonna tell you mine!
And nobody's dying until that happens, okay?
Good grief.
That pipsqueak really runs hard, doesn't he?
I don't recall giving you permission to butt into my fight for me!
Should I burn you as well?
He's part of the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
They've plunged the kingdom into confusion and taken a massive toll on its people.
They are not interested in swapping stories!
Now move!
Even if it means killing them all, we must stop them.
Yeah?
Why is that?
We're the same, aren't we?
So we should be able to talk things over.
Both sides are mad because we lost someone we loved.
I've been thinking a lot about this.
Everyone's fighting because we can't forgive the other side.
So how do we get rid of all that anger and hatred?
I know I'm not very smart, so I can't come up with the right answer.
But we can do it!
I mean, we have to, don't we?
My goal.
The future that I worked so hard to build.
I believe it isn't that far off.
Whether you're nobility, a citizen, or just a commoner.
Or even if you're not a human.
It's a future that all of you will create.
A nation that's free of hatred and prejudice.
I just want a kingdom where all of us get along and laugh together.
And when I'm the Wizard King, we'll have one.
You'll see.
You imbecile.
Proudly proclaiming something so outrageous.
I think he's actually serious.
In fact, it reminds me of what someone else said once before.
This little one here is the key to our future.
The bridge that will unite the elves and humankind.
Congratulations, Licta Tetya.
Congratulations!
If only the rest of the human race thought about it the way these guys do.
Then maybe...
No.
It's too late to stop now.
Hey, welcome back!
Took you long enough.
You snagged the last of the magic stones, right?
Watch your tongue, Radies.
Everything went as we planned.
In fact, even better.
Our Master Lict has assassinated the Wizard King.
Seriously?
That's awesome!
Wow, Master Lict!
Great going!
The time has come.
There's not a soul who can stand in our way anymore.
Come on.
Just a little longer.
When Owen gets here, he's gonna fix you right up.
That leader was so powerful.
He could have easily killed everyone in the land.
Even without collecting all of the magic stones.
That means he must be after something else.
I fear that Clover Kingdom may yet suffer a devastating fate.
I let him steal the stones.
I'm sorry.
Such a failure is below the Wizard King.
Forget that.
You just saved thousands of lives.
I hope we make it to him in time.
Marks is going to be so disappointed in me for the way things ended.
It's a shame that I won't be there when Vigolion finally wakes up.
Yami.
There are still so many things.
Things I wanted to tell you.
Don't go talking like that.
You can't check out on me now.
That's something I can't forgive.
Because I still haven't...
Look at that freak.
He's not from here, you know.
He washed up from some other country.
Lives alone on the coast.
I wish he'd just go back where he belongs.
Wow!
Was that dark magic?
What the...
Awesome!
I've never seen it before.
Please, you've got to let me get a closer look.
Yeah, no.
Who are you, mister?
I...
Oh, well, I'm no one to be suspicious of.
I assure you, I'm just a magic knight captain out walking in disguise.
What's a magic knight, captain?
Huh?
You don't know that?
Okay.
Why don't you come with me and I'll show you?
I think you have real potential.
See this, Yami?
It's how you write your name here.
Oh, great.
I'm never going to remember a bunch of squiggly lines like that.
Well, if you practice, you'll pick it up in no time.
I don't want to.
Aww.
But if you learn to write, I'll buy dinner for you.
I'm on it.
You haven't been on the squad for very long.
But I'm already astonished by everything you've accomplished.
That said, I'd rather you didn't run too wild.
We've had some, well...
Uh-oh.
Look.
It's the enemy.
Then let's go.
But reel it in a little.
Yeah!
Well, we'll work on that later.
And Yami, from this moment on, you will be recognized as founder and leader of the Black Bulls.
Best of luck, captain.
Yami, I'm leaving the rest to you now.
Yes, sir.
I got to meet so many people and see so many spells.
It was a fun life.
A good life.
Julius.
Don't you worry, friend.
We'll keep the kingdom safe for you.
I can't help but wonder how everyone's doing.
I've been casting my spatial jamming spell for several hours.
It's getting rather difficult to hold my arms up.
But this is no time for complaining.
The Royal Knights are in there battling the Eye of the Midnight Sun with everything they've got.
The future of the Clover Kingdom hangs in the balance.
Please, team.
Do your very best.
Hey!
Look up there!
What's that?
It's an abundance of mana!
We're headed straight for the center.
You guys, be careful!
I don't care who crosses us.
I'm not in the mood to lose.
Neither am I!
Let's go knock them dead, you know!
This place is so bizarre.
Yes.
Is that a person?
The mana.
It's so...
Yes.
It's unbelievably powerful.
All it needs now is the last of the magic stones.
We'll awaken our true might with the Monument of the Tree of Life to guide our every step.
Yes.
The fateful day that we've waited for has arrived.
Yeah, since we were lucky enough to be chosen by the mana, our magic powers are about to go through the roof!
Ha!
This is gonna be fun!
Those magic knights will be dead before they even figure out what hit them!
With our new power, plus my dark magic items will be unbeatable!
Oh, I can hardly wait!
Soon I'll get my hands on Asa and experiment to my heart's content!
Enough!
This newfound advantage is to be used solely to establish the society Master Licht has envisioned.
You know, Master, if we'd never become acquainted with you, we'd still be eking out the same lonely, pathetic existence, despised by everyone.
But you, you gladly welcomed us into the eye of the midnight sun, changing our lives.
Master Licht, I've been happy to serve, even if we were but a small help.
Are you done yet?
Because I can only listen to so much kissing up before I puke!
Anyway, it's looking like we'll be able to wreak even more havoc, so you know I'm in!
And my research will be extra helpful after we get this boost!
Yes, you three have done well during our time together.
Thank you for that.
And please know that I'm exceedingly proud of your efforts.
At last, the time has come to fulfill our highest goal.
The rebirth of our true forms to create our new kingdom.
Yes, sir!
Hey!
Since I met you all, I have been speaking as Licht, your humble leader.
Huh?
From now on, I will express my true feelings instead.
You have acted out of greed and selfishness, casually harming others while prioritizing your own interest above everything else.
You hate, envy, and discriminate against your fellow human beings for the most fleeting of reasons.
And then you justify your sins and shortcomings with your blind devotion to me.
All for the sake of your lousy, filthy, disgusting selves.
Humans really are the self-serving shameful worms I always knew you were.
You're absolutely irredeemable.
Master, I don't understand.
This is where we must bid each other farewell.
The great rebirth will start with you.
That bright light, it's from the Forsaken Room.
You are so much more.
You have to 준비 each other for your own hassle.
They are so much more.
We made hello 그건.
Oh no!
What is going on here?
You have to leave your quietly.
No!
The rain is to 그림.
The rain is to visible.
And you are so many images.
I will rub my algún tree.
Well, look at that. It's finally begun.
What are you talking about?
This power just shot through the roof.
Hey, something's not right.
This is it.
Today we're going to assume our true forms and reclaim our old strength.
What's happening?
Whatever power he's wielding, it's not human mana.
Listen, let's get out!
You know, what's wrong?
I don't need no money, I don't need no魔力はいらない。
自力で挑んだミラクル起きること願い
微力ながら1ミリずつビリビリ切り込んでく
世界を巻き込んでく
My disability is my ability
逆にそれが俺のエネルギー
どうしても自らを見失って
嫌いになって
負けそうになったら
Just cry out loud
傷つく音に
立ち向かう勇気へと導いてく
Our treasure
くなぎらないのは
最高に there is love
かざした近い光が
生きる
TREASURE
We'll cradle
lol
Most how our life love
が
ハイティブ było
マシスト
ずつも
Twiday
国呼ぶ
democrat
電 oss
レッタイソウル
ペナロン
エプロー
ワイ チャビ
今
彼は
Can you tell me what this one says?
How should I know?
This one, then.
Nope, not a clue.
Okay.
I told you I'm never going to be able to learn all this stuff.
You have no idea how crappy my memory is.
Be strong.
It isn't good to set limits for yourself.
Even if it seems hopeless to you now,
if you believe in yourself,
then you can push beyond any obstacle.
I want to unite this kingdom, whatever it takes.
So that everyone can laugh together,
regardless of their magic, status, or background.
It may sound like a lofty dream,
but I have no doubt it can be done.
Push beyond my limits.
Okay, then.
How do you write like that?
Ah, now you're motivated.
Let's try the last question.
What's this?
Left.
We're not testing your eyesight.
Too long have my people and I
been forced to trod under the burden
of sadness and solitude.
But now that too has reached its end.
Black Clover, page 95.
Reincarnation.
I shall destroy humankind.